The Swap is a comedy, tv movie film directed by Jay Karas.
Based on the book by Megan Shull, The Swap follows the adventures of a rhythmic gymnast named Ellie with a make-it-or-break-it
competition, and the younger brother named Jack in a hockey family who's vying for a varsity spot on his school team.
But when a simple text causes the two to swap bodies,
their paths take an unexpected cross.
Ellie O'Brien, played by Peyton List.
Jack Malloy, played by Jacob Bertrand.
Coach Malloy, played by Darrin Rose.
Summer, played by Claire Rankin.
Gunner, played by Callan Potter.
Stryker, played by Jesse Bostick.
The Swap is a 2016 American television teen film that premiered on Disney Channel as
a part of the network's annual "Monstober" event on October 7, 2016.
The film is based on the young adult novel of the same name written by Megan Shull and is
written by Charlie Shahnaian and Shari Simpson and directed by Jay Karas.
The movie stars Peyton List and Jacob Bertrand.
The film explores themes of high school, based on novel or
book, ice hockey, body-swap, rhythmic gymnastics.
The tone is lighthearted.